foodlion.com 2010-12-26

# About Us: Privacy Statement

  * Press Room
  * Vendors
  * Company Charter
  * Core Values
  * Animal Welfare
  * History
  * Legal Terms & Conditions
  * Fast Facts
  * Privacy Statement
  * Current Promotions
  * Community Involvement

English | Spanish

**Our Online Data Collection and Use Practices**  
This statement explains the online data collection and use practices of Foodlion.com; the statement and its description of our online data practices does not apply to other online sites or to other services provided by Food Lion, LLC, Delhaize America, Inc. or the Delhaize Group. This statement does not apply to the offline data collection and use practices of Food Lion, LLC, Delhaize America, Inc. or the Delhaize Group, such as data collection in a Food Lion Store. Please be aware that this privacy statement and the choices you make on this site will not necessarily apply to personal information you may have provided or will provide to Food Lion in other settings.

Since Internet technologies continue to evolve and Internet business models are not fully established, this statement is subject to change. Any changes to the privacy statement will be posted on this page and we will notify you of any material changes by placing a prominent notice on the home page of Foodlion.com. We encourage you to periodically visit this page to stay informed about the data practices of Foodlion.com. By using this site, you consent to the data practices described on this page and any updates.

**The Information We Collect On This Site**  
Foodlion.com maintains and uses the anonymous, non-personal information collected in our server log files. This information includes such anonymous data as number of visitors to the site, most popular pages, the user's operating system (for example, Macintosh or Windows), and user's browser type (for example, Netscape Navigator or Internet Explorer). We use this information to help us improve our website and enhance your viewing experience. The server log files do not collect email addresses or other personally identifying information. We do not tie this information to personal data and therefore it remains anonymous.

**Surveys**  
The information we gather from online surveys on the Foodlion.com site is for Foodlion.com use only. We generally do not request personally identifiable information such as name or email address in connection with our surveys. If we publish the results of a survey online, the information is in a collective, non-personally identifiable form.

**Cookies**  
Our website uses persistent cookies to identify unique visitors and personalize your viewing experience. For example, we may store your zip code so we can display the stores closest to you. We do not correlate Cookie information with any personally identifying information such as name, address or email address.

**The Information You Provide**  
There are a number of places on this website where you can sign up for a promotion, register for an MVP Card, request information, apply for a job, or otherwise participate in a program offered by Foodlion.com or by other companies on the Foodlion.com site. You may be asked to provide personal information in connection with these activities. Personal information may include your name, address, e-mail, credit card information, MVP Card number, etc. This section will describe how Foodlion.com collects and uses the personal information you provide to Foodlion.com on the Foodlion.com site. This section does not apply to the data collection practices of other companies that may offer a program or activity jointly with Foodlion.com.

When you change your MVP Card information, get additional or replacement MVP Cards, or participate in the Lion Shop & Share program, we require personal information such as your name, mailing address, and phone number to administer the MVP Card program, to provide you with the information or service you requested, and to perform analyses of our services. We do not share this information with outside parties, however, we have hired outside companies to assist us in administering the program, and to complete your request, deliver customized promotional offers to you, such as additional savings and to perform statistical analyses of our services. Foodlion.com will provide those other companies with the information they need to perform the services and we prohibit them from using the information for other purposes. Please be aware that we do not view subsidiaries and affiliates of Food Lion as outside parties or outside companies and that we may periodically share personal information or aggregated information with Food Lion subsidiaries and affiliates.

You may also be asked to provide personal information such as your name, address, email address and phone number when you participate in contests or promotional offers from Foodlion.com or from other companies on the Foodlion.com site. When this information is submitted to Foodlion.com, it is used to administer the contest or promotional offer, and also to provide you with the information or service you requested. We do not control how other companies use the information you may provide to them and recommend that you check the Privacy Statement of the company requesting information for a description of their data collection practices. We do not share this information except where we have hired an outside company to administer the service, program or contest or perform statistical analyses of our services, or where the activity is sponsored by another company. As we noted above, Foodlion.com does not view subsidiaries and affiliates of Food Lion as outside companies and we may periodically share personal information or aggregated information with Food Lion subsidiaries and affiliates.

In addition, Foodlion.com collects personal information when you voluntarily submit it to us, for example, when you apply for a job or email consumer relations. We have no obligation of any kind with respect to such information except as provided in this privacy statement. We use such information internally for the purposes collected and we treat any comments, suggestions and the like as public information.

The Foodlion.com site provides links to third party sites such as supermarkets.com, Food Lion Credit Association (foodlionca.org) and Ralston Purina (purina.com) as a service to our viewers and associates. You may be asked to provide personal information in connection with activities on such third party sites. Please be aware that Foodlion.com does not control such third party sites, does not endorse their content and is not responsible for the data collection and use practices of these other sites. Foodlion.com encourages you to be aware when you leave the Foodlion.com site and to read the privacy statements of each and every web site that collects personal information. This privacy statement does not apply to third party sites; it applies solely to information collected by Foodlion.com on this site.

Food Lion is a dynamic company and continues to develop its business. In that connection, Food Lion might buy or sell divisions or assets. In such transactions, User information generally is one of the transferred assets.

**How to Change or Delete Your Information**  
If you have submitted personally identifiable information through our website and would like to change or delete that information, please call 1-800-210-9569 or contact us via [email](http://apps.foodlion.com/CustomerRelations/default.aspx). In your email, please tell us which page or form on the website you used to submit your information.

**Our Data Security Measures**  
Rest assured that we have put into place physical, electronic and managerial procedures to prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, ensure the correct use of information and safeguard and secure the information we collect about you. However, Foodlion.com cannot guarantee that unauthorized access or disclosure of information will never occur.

**Children's Privacy**  
Foodlion.com does not collect or maintain information at our website from those we actually know are under 13. From time to time we may display information that is specifically aimed at children, for example coloring pages. However, registration is never required to access these pages and we do not collect personal information in connection with these activities.

**Restrictions**  
Foodlion.com may disclose personal information if required to do so by law or if we believe such action is necessary to comply with legal process served on Foodlion.com. If information received is harmful, obscene, threatening, criminal or has criminal implications, we reserve the right to use, disseminate, or store this information as we deem appropriate in our sole and absolute discretion.

**Your Consent**  
By using our website, you agree to the conditions of this privacy statement. We reserve the right to change this privacy statement. If we change the statement, we will post the changes on this page to keep you informed of the information we collect, how we use this information, and whether the information is shared with third parties. Your continued use of the site constitutes your agreement to this privacy statement and any updates.

**How to Contact Us**  
Should you have other questions or concerns about this privacy statement or our data collection practices, please call us at 1-800-210-9569.
